Try to balance all these things.
[music]
So much has happened since the last
study [music] vlog in the sense that
like it's been a month. But this
morning,
[music]
>> this morning I have a test at 9:00 a.m.
I need to do [music] some reviewing
beforehand.
Yeah.
I don't know where my
face towel is.
>> [sighs]
>> Okay, [music] I'm going to attempt a
basil level of talking.
>> This test isn't a big deal. I wouldn't
know. I haven't [music] done it yet. So,
going to use my dressing.
I've been using two moisturizers
actually. This is my like original one
that I go to. I used to use the Kles,
but I haven't bothered to repurchase it.
This one's another one. Prefer when I'm
doing heavy like going out makeup
because otherwise it just makes my skin
feel a little bit oily. This one's a
little bit lighter for everyday. advice
for you guys.
[snorts]
So quiet.
It's like
Put some Jokers on.
So, it has [music] been a while.
Something tastes soft.
Tastes really bad.
Maybe it was that almond milk. That
tastes really bad.
Oh my gosh. Okay,
I think the fact that that tasted awful
has woken me up in itself. I'm just
going to get a coffee on the way to uni.
For now, it is 6:13 a.m. [music] and I
have a test, like a little quiz. I guess
you could call it a midterm. I've got a
lecture part first and then like a quiz.
So, I'm not sure if she's doing revision
first. But there are some things I want
to go over because these are things I
have to look over anyways, obviously.
For med statistics, [music] I actually
did a study with me yesterday, which
should already be uploaded depending on
which video I get edited first. Probably
that one. But yeah, let's
do some productive work. 6:15
in the morning and then head to uni.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay. I need to get ready. I need to get
dressed. But I also want to do some more
questions. But I also need breakfast.
I thought I ran out of blueberries, but
found some sitting in my fridge. So,
It's good. It's good. It's okay.
Definitely better than the coffee. So,
that's good. At least
I have just about 15 minutes until I
need to leave. So, I'm going to do my
makeup.
Um, Maria just sent me her notes,
so that's what I'm reading through while
I'm waiting for my setting [music] spray
to dry. Okay.
5 minutes. We're in good time. Now I can
pack my bag.
Good morning.
>> Good morning. [laughter]
This is called blood pressure zippers
and we are going to see which test and
we create that create the grouping and
these two groups that are created there
is no overlap between the groups and
measurements. I want each observation to
my sample.
>> So the lecture part is over and turns
out we don't have biochem lab today
which I'm annoyed about. So I'm not sure
what I'm going to do after this. What
are we going to do?
>> We get coffee. We'll get coffee for a
bit, maybe go to a study cafe, but we're
about to do the quiz. So,
>> brought my lab coat and everything. And
we don't even have biochem today. So,
we're just going to go to have a little
quaff.
>> No, no, no. I'm I already eat a lovely
omelette.
I was wondering cuz it might make things
easier.
>> Will you just drop everything in there?
>> I was saving so much time. [music]
>> They were selected.
only just got let out of bio. I
struggled to make my blood class cuz
it's 3:30 now. It's really difficult to
keep a high morale and keep motivated,
especially in this runup to Christmas.
She is give you guys a vlog from my
perspective. Um, I got home. Doy came
me.
>> I did my bed. I didn't I
>> And now we're eating at One Piece. But
it's healthy. It's a Poké Ball, guys.
>> Yeah. Plus a bit.
>> So, I got changed. I've been trying to
get awake for an hour now. Over an hour.
But I'm awake and I've got to leave in 5
minutes. Well, actually in Greece, we
have like 15 minutes after the lecture
actually starts, so technically I won't
be late. I won't be late. The test
yesterday wasn't [clears throat]
actually that demanding for medical
statistics. I'm glad with how it went.
I'm way too tired. And today is an even
longer day with lectures. I've been
trying to get back to the library, but I
think I'm so like adamant against the
library because I associate it with exam
season. This is what my lectures are
looking like today. I'm trying to do my
best.
I'm tired. Last night we had a little
birthday dinner for my [music] friend.
>> Yes.
>> Cheers.
I'm
>> trying to balance all [music] these
things. And when people tell you like
balance is the most important thing.
It's easier said than done quite
literally. [music]
I'm actually really enjoying
biochemistry this semester. Not that
it's easier than [music] last semester,
but I find it more interesting because
it's definitely more bio than care for
sure. And I prefer biology to chemistry.
Physiology is very similar to
hisystologology this semester in the
sense that they coincide in subjects. If
we're doing the respiratory system or
the urinary system in histologology, we
will then go on to do them in
physiology.
But a double
photo espresso. I think I ordered that
in Greek. I'll ask how to say that in
Greek class later on.
Okay,
it's it's 9:12. Let's see if the lecture
started.
So
immune response
happens you have the complex which is
composed of molecule and so uh this is
oversimplified.
I know some of the molecules I mentioned
to you, but
anyway, we see this process. We're going
to do that.
>> This excites me. [laughter]
We have
on the left side.
Yes. Hi.
for me.
>> I love it.
I'm just so like
[laughter]
>> Have you seen the grandma who goes blah
boo?
[laughter]
So it comes to the like grow like red
like if I was like
>> the urinary system part of essentials
like electroly
can be found and no sodium is left in
the unit because it's very useful
the black are off of the white lens on
the this morning
I've got green glass and I'm
I genuinely feel
so exhausted and for some reason at the
beginning of the week I was very
optimistic thinking I would have a
bouncer full of energy after a full day
of lectures. I booked myself a gym class
at 6:30,
which I could theoretically cancel, but
I don't want to be blocked from my gym
app.
I think she
Got my towel again.